Nishant Sharma

DevOps Engineer



About Me

Dedicated to optimization, and understands the melding of operations and development to quickly deliver code to customers; Has intermediate experience with the Cloud and monitoring processes as well as DevOps development in Windows, Mac, and Linux systems.

Experience

Cloudoric R&D Pvt Ltd

DevOps Engineer

2021 - Present

- Work with Site Reliability Engineers to obtain DevOps skills.
- · Work with Observability and Monitoring team.

Rapidcode Technologies Private Limited

Cloud Practitioner

2020 - 2021

- Develop and implement technical efforts to design, build, and deploy AWS applications within the direction of lead architects.
- Adding users to a cloud infrastructure, permissions,
 Adding or changing workflow process.

Skills

AWS - IAM, EC2, ELB etc.

• • • • •

Kubernetes - EKS

Terraform

Logs shipping and monitoring

• • • • •

Education

2016 - 2020

B.TECH - Computer Science

& Engineering

G.J.U.S.T - Hisar

_

Contact Info

Address

Aligarh - UTTAR PRADESH

Email

nishantsharma9358@gmail.com

Phone

+91 8218006942

Portfolio

github.com/thecyberbaby

Language

English

Hindi